This week, NBC premiered Nurses. The ratings were not good but this show was already renewed before it aired. If not, we would have predicted this show to be a certain cancellation.

Coroner drops from a certain renewal to just leaning renewed.

FBI and SEAL Team both drop from certain to likely renewals.

Bob ♥ Abishola upgrades from leaning to likely renewal.

The Unicorn upgrades from leaning towards cancellation to leaning towards renewal.

MacGyver upgrades from a likely cancellation to leaning towards renewal.

Pandora, Blue Bloods, and B Positive all upgrade from likely cancellations to just leaning canceled.

S.W.A.T. upgrades all the way from a certain cancellation to leaning towards renewal.

Mom upgrades from a certain cancellation to just leaning canceled.